Everyone!
After we kick Kaido's ass,
we'll have a huge feast!
– Yeah!
Outta my way, you weaklings!
Jaggy!
I won't let anyone else take Kaido's head!
Right, Killer?
Right.
Kaido, you better make yourself presentable!
'Cause I'm gonna take that ugly mug of yours
and mount it on the bow of my ship!
Damn straight!
How dare you turn Killer into a jolly guy?!
We'll just become a jolly pirate crew, then!
Stop it!
Smell you later, Straw Hat!
Hey, wait, Jaggy!
That bastard!
They're in a good mood!
Jinbe! You know what to do!
Keep up with Jaggy's ship!
Sounds fun! Alright!
Leave it to me!
I'll catch up to that punk's ship in no time!
About ship!
Wow! Cool!
You're a pro, Jinbe!
After them!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
Just you wait, Kaido!
Now then, just as we planned...
See you at the rear gate!
Nin, nin!
Sir Law! I am counting on you!
Onward!
Submerge!
– Aye, aye, sir!
Adjust trim, 30 degrees!
Adjusting trim, 30 degrees!
Sustain a depth of 100 meters!
Captain! What's our course?!
Full speed ahead to
the rear gate of Onigashima!
– Aye, aye, sir!
Everyone!
Stay vigilant!
Do not let your guard down!
There could be an ambush any minute!
Are you as sharp as I remember, Denjiro?
Why bother surviving the last
two decades if not to hone my skills?
I suppose you are, then!
Let us finish this!
Yes!
There it is...
So this is Onigashima!
It's enormous!
I've never seen it before.
So this is Kaido's stronghold!
Kin, look.
I know...
They are simply enjoying a banquet...
without a single guard on duty.
I suppose they have not received
Kanjuro's report yet...
Or perhaps they have received it,
but they remain unconcerned...
Regardless, we are fortunate...
Now we can launch a surprise attack!
Kaido's castle is pretty far inland, right?
Yeah, looks like it!
It's farther from here than we expected.
If they haven't noticed yet,
we should attack quickly...
What's that?
Is that a guard?!
What are those?
Ships?
Huh? You've gotta be kidding!
I didn't hear anything about this!
Why don't you guys take a nap?!
Lethal Green Star!
Sleepgrass!
Oh?
I thought I saw some people there...
They just dozed off!
Problem solved!
Easy peasy!
I see...
I have a rough understanding of the plan...
but if we moor this many
ships out in the open,
it will surely alert our enemies!
Prepare to disembark!
What's going on?
Don't tell me they...
Destroy them!
– What?!
What?! What?! What's all this about?!
What are they doing?!
You sank the ships to hide them?!
But you can't sail them now!
How are you guys gonna get back?!
You just cut off your own escape!
Sir Luffy, you need not worry.
Let them all sink!
For on this mission...
we need no return ships!
With that said, we must
advance. Please excuse us!
Keep a low profile, men!
What an incredible display of true resolve...
from those samurai warriors.
No hesitation...
only determination...
Win or die...
There can be no arrogance
when taking on an Emperor!
What if they wanna escape?!
They'll be swallowed by the sea...
Th-Then...
Then...
Does that mean we have to sink the Sunny?!
No way, you dumbasses!
A small number of ships can be hidden!
You all should make your way ashore as well!
Alright! I'll do it!
What?!
No way!
Oh no!
What is it, Carrot?
Look!
How did we not notice...?
The shore is packed with enemies!
No, it's not.
Oh?
Look at the other end of the bridge!
Hey! What's with this?!
It's what the enemy wears.
Do you like it?
That's one of my special techniques!
Garb-Garb Kin's Clothing Company!
It appears...
some mighty pirates stand before me.
You may invade this island as you like...
but we face a formidable force!
They outnumber us five to one.
So I advise you to take
advantage of those disguises!
Good thinking.
We just wanna take down Kaido.
We don't have time for all the lackeys...
Let's go!
Yeah.
Sir Luffy!
Perhaps you should all pass through it as well!
Yeah! That looks like fun!
I'm gonna do it, too!
Transform!
Hup!
Cool!
Ta-da!
Chobro! You look amazing!
I'm going through, too!
Nami! You're even more tantalizing!
Now let me try it!
How do I look?
Same as usual.
Don't you even care
enough to make fun of me?
Robin, you're such a badass beauty!
We're gonna do it, too!
– Yay!
Super!
Now, since they were made by my technique,
once you remove or tear them,
your original kimono will reappear!
My fellow warriors!
This is Onigashima, Kaido's stronghold!
Avoid unnecessary battles whenever possible,
and try to reach the castle for the final battle!
Good luck!
That hits the spot!
Now that we're free from
the ghosts of the Kozuki Clan,
this booze tastes absolutely divine!
Orochi is feeling carefree.
Thanks to the spy Kanjuro informing
him of the Red Scabbards' plans,
he conjured a foolproof plan
to counter their insurrection.
Their rendezvous point is Tokage Port!
Destroy all routes that lead there!
The Red Scabbards are scattered
and helpless! Be sure you kill them all!
He will no longer be tormented
by the ghosts of the Kozuki Clan.
However, at Onigashima...
The raid has begun!
The eastern forces led by Kin'emon.
The southern forces led by Denjiro.
Combined, there are more than 5,000 troops.
The pirate Law's submarine...
has submerged with the
Red Scabbards samurai on board.
Its course has been set for the castle
where Orochi and Kaido are.
Their enemies are still unaware
of the 5,000 advancing troops.
Hey, what's taking you so long?
Hurry up, Franky!
Everyone's already left.
Give me a second.
We'll catch up to them in no time...
if we use this!
Black Rhino FR-U4!
Yay!
I remember it from
the battle at Fishman Island!
Not "it," Jinbe!
Call this baby the Black Rhino!
And there's another one!
Brachio-Tank 5!
I'm in charge of this tank!
Commander Chopper, reporting!
We're counting on you, Chopper!
Great! We can get there safely!
Chobro, you're so cool!
You're in good hands!
And I'm the gunner!
Chopper!
Usopp!
Franky!
– We're here!
Now we're all ready!
Where's Luffy?
Well...
Eustass Kid and his crew
headed straight into the island, so...
Okay!
I'm gonna go stop them!
Don't worry!
– He's only gonna make things worse!
Why didn't you stop him?!
Roronoa Zoro said the same, but then...
Luffy's only gonna make things worse!
I'm gonna go stop him!
– He'll just get lost in there!
Is that so...?
Forget about that moron!
Let's go on a ride through
the battlefield, Nami!
It's full!
Get out, Usopp!
Damn you! You're in heaven!
I'm sorry you can't aim like me!
Get over it!
How about you ride with me?
Can I?
I'd be happy to.
Okay, I'm ready.
You?!
What's wrong with a little bromance?
Alright, fine.
Commander Chopper!
Yeah?
Meet me at the back of the island,
and we'll dock these vehicles together.
Good luck!
"Docking"!
Super!
Roger!
I feel like a rock star!
Are you a haunted doll or something?!
We should go, too!
Robin my love!
Come with me!
No thanks.
You'll get dusty on top of the tank.
Shall we walk?
Sure.
You guys are as lively as ever.
In a battle where everyone's pumped up,
it's key to have someone
who can observe things calmly.
You're so mature.
It's quite reassuring.
I want to be helpful in my
first battle as part of this crew!
Hey! Keep walking!
Kanjuro and the captive Momonosuke...
have yet to reach Orochi,
just as Kin'emon surmised.
I've never been down here before.
I had no idea it was such a labyrinth.
From the perspective of these
ignorant bit players,
I'm still one of the Red Scabbards...
I must report on Kin'emon
and the others as soon as possible.
How can I get to Lord Orochi?!
Dearest Lord Kaido!
My word, it's been ages!
Why do you keep talking like that?
Are you drinking?
There's no point in drinking with grunts.
I wanna drink with you, Kaido!
Yeah,
sounds good.
We'll go to the hall later.
No standing on ceremony today.
Why can't we go now?
I was gonna introduce
you guys to Linlin first...
but I heard she's changing.
So let's see her later.
Anyway, there was a small incident,
so I had to keep you guys waiting.
You call this planning?!
Hey! Stop!
Yeah, I know, but it wasn't me that
summoned you guys in the first place.
– Huh?!
– What?!
Well, then who did?
It was me.
I summoned them here, Kaido.
King...
What the hell would you need from us?!
You bastard! Why trick us?!
If you had known it was at my request, some of you wouldn't have come.
Who's-Who! Sasaki!
You got that right.
You two were once captains
of your own pirate crews...
and now you're aiming for
our positions as the Superstars.
In this group, merit decides the hierarchy.
So of course we're aiming high!
Know your place.
Alright, enough!
Why are you bickering on
the day of our special feast?
King! Why did you summon them?
Because I was the first to hear
about your little incident.
So don't you need them?
I do, indeed...
Bao Huang!
Coming!
What's my schedule today?
Later at the Golden Festival stage
where Queen is performing now...
the three Superstars
and Master Fukurokuju will...
make a toast!
Following that, Lord Orochi
and Lord Kaido will...
give speeches!
Then, when the Big Mom Pirates' ship arrives...
Lord Kaido and Big Mom
will announce the world's strongest...
pirate alliance!
After that, Lord Kaido will make...
an important announcement!
That's it.
An important announcement?!
It's not like you to keep us waiting, Kaido.
That's the very height of annoyance!
Yeah, I know.
But if I reveal it now,
it'll only cause confusion.
Now, here is what I want you guys to do.
My idiot son Yamato disappeared today,
so I want you to bring him to me!
Whoa...
That's quite a task.
That must mean your announcement
involves Young Master Yamato?
That's right.
I see.
What a pain! It's just a family matter!
Hey!
And...
what if we bring him back safely?
I'll give you the right to challenge
the Superstar of your choice.
How's that?
Seriously?
I'll do it!
I'm in, too!
You don't mind, do you?
No.
Not at all!
What is this?
They made too much.
Why bring it here?
We had no choice!
Jaggy!
Where are you?!
He doesn't even know about Oden's wish!
Why did he go off on his own?!
Hey! Have you seen Jaggy?!
Jaggy? Who's that?
If I get thinner, I'll be too popular
So I don't get thinner, that's my kind of...
funk!
It's that balloon guy!
You're late!
Why don't you eat, too?
Huh?
This way! This way!
Yeah.
Wow!
Everything looks so delicious!
Why don't you chow down, too?
Really?!
The entire harvest from
Halcyon Farm is ours alone to enjoy!
If the people of Okobore Town ate one bite,
they'd die of shock from the rich taste!
Take it already!
I told you I don't want it!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
Hey, what's that?
It's oshiruko!
But we're drinking now!
Screw you!
Oshiruko?
They made too much, so the rest is ours.
Dumbass!
It doesn't go with alcohol!
There's plenty of stuff to eat!
Just trash it!
This soup is way too sweet!
Let's dump it all over Okobore Town!
Good idea!
They'll happily lap it up off the ground!
It's so yummy!
This soup is so delicious!
What? Is this your first time having it?!
Yes!
There's even mochi in it!
What a fancy treat!
This is the greatest day of my life!
Damn beggars!
Just be happy you're alive!